SADIK AHMAD SADI

Honors In Economics



CONTACTS



KhadimNagar, Airport, Sadar, Sylhet.



(+88) 01731030271



OBJECTIVE

Seeking an innovative & challenging position that will maximize opportunities to implement my knowledge, skills & experience, and utilization of my capabilities that will not only enrich me but also lead to the overall development of an organization.

INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

- Strong leadership
- Communication
- Presentation
- Motivation
- **Learning Spirit**
- Responsibility
- Positive attitude

PROFILE SUMMARY

4 Month experienced TIB as field annumatort with 14 days tryning.

1 year experienced on teaching sector from an private High school.

Strong Training & Volunteering professional with a Bachelor of Social scince (BSS) honors focused in Economics from MC College, Sylhet under National University.

WORK EXPERIENCE

High School Teacher (Private)

Jan 2018 - Decembor-2018

For upgrading Myself and gather knowledge and skill to Join this private institute.

Youth Advocate BRAC

Sep 2018 - Present

Right Here Right Now-Bangladesh Platform



Creating awareness among young girls & boys on sexual reproductive health and rights.

Youth advocate Ida

Jan2018 - Present

Creating awareness among young girls & boys on sexual reproductive health and rights.

Yes friend TIB

Jun 2018 - present

A Garman base institute raised voice against Corruptions

Organizing secretary

May 2019 – Dec 2022

Student Forum of Chatol.

TRAINING & WORKSHOP

- 15 days training on survey questionnaire, sampling ,techniques, listing methods, respondant interviews and others relevant matters, under Transparency International Bangladesh (TIB)
- Youth Advocate Training on Sexual and Reproductive Health and Rights (SRHR) organized by BRAC for 3 days
- Workshop on 'English for Career' organized by The Phoenix for 1 day
- Workshop on 'Bangla for Career' organized by The Phoenix for 1 day
- Accept 7 days training by Upozila porisonkan Buru for PHC.

SADIK AHMAD SADI

Hnours Economics

STRENGTH

- Proven experience working as a skilled teacher.
- Proficiency in Microsoft Office applications.
- Strong negotiation and consultative skills.
- Excellent organizational and problem-solving skills.
- Effective communication skills.
- Exceptional volunteer service skills.
- Confident and friendly.

IT SKILLS

- MS Word, Excel, PowerPoint
- Adb Photoshop ,Illustrator
- Email correspondents&Internet browsing, etc.

LANGUAGE

- Bengali Mother Tongue
- English Professional proficiency

REFERENCE

Md Sahmim Mia

Assistant Professor

Department of Economics.

MC College, Sylhet.

Mobile:+8801723338732

CONFERENCE

- BRAC Conference 2015 at BCDM Savar organized by- BRAC Education programme
- National Level SRHR knowledge Sharing Conference, organized by BRAC Education programme
- National Conference: Youth in Leadership and Sexual and Reproductive Health and Rights, organized by RHRN - Bangladesh Platform at Gonoshasthaya Kendra, Savar, Dhaka

EDUCATIONS

2022

Bachelor of Social Scince (BSS-Honors) in Economics

MC College, Sylhet (National University) CGPA – 2.97 out of 4.00

2016 Higher Secondary Certificate (HSC)

Border Guard public School and College, Sylhet

SylhetBoard | Humanities GPA -4.25 out of 5.00

Secondary School Certificate (SSC)
Shahialal University School, Sylhet

Shahjalal University School Sylhet SylhetBoard | Humanities

GPA - 4.44.00 out of 5

PERSONAL DETAILS

Father's Name: Mokbul Ali

Mother's Name: Mayarun Nessa

Nationality : Bangladeshi (by birth)

Date of Birth: 14 april 1998.

Marital Status : Single

Permanent Address: KhadimNagar,

Airport, Sadar, Sylhet

and

Sadik Ahmad Sadi .